♪A beam of light penetrates
through the dust♪
♪Through meridians, bright and dim♪
♪Tearing apart the gloom♪
♪Unbreakable threads of love♪
♪Bewilder the mind♪
♪Brushing off the snow with a turn♪
♪Who approaches?♪
♪Unable to resist the stormy burial♪
♪Bound and entangled,
the line between black and white blurs♪
♪The skeletal remains
beneath my feet lowly roar♪
♪Saying we aren't born with power♪
♪Staining the vast sky
with blood to ignite♪
♪A rebellious battle♪
♪Awaiting the rebirth
of a slumbering heart♪
♪Phoenix-like♪
♪Until the boundless firmament♪
♪Fills it for me♪
♪In every corner of heaven and earth♪
♪Mountains, rivers, seas and more♪
♪I reign supreme♪
[The Proud Emperor of Eternity S1 (Pt 1)]
[Episode 1]
[Purple Scale Beast]
[Liu Fei, store owner]
You struck gold once more.
Thanks.
If you're tired,
you can take a break in a room here.
Interesting.
You can't slip from my grasp.
Is Ms. Liu sweet on this guy now?
This is the renowned Fierce!
Fierce?
(He's now)
(a master who has made it
onto the Tian Ranking,)
(referred to as Fierce
by the martial world.)
After all this time,
do you...
[Lin Rou, the eldest daughter
of the Lin family]
do you...
still not get
that I have feelings for you?
You already have a fiance.
Fiance?
That guy's destined to be just a nobody.
I have...
no interest in him.
He's a total loser who can't cultivate,
so of course you have no interest in him.
But unfortunately,
Ms. Lin,
I also have no interest in you.
No one has ever dared
to treat me this way!
[Chu Kuangsheng, the eldest son
of the Chu family]
Chu Qing, you're being too much!
I think it's a good suggestion.
Liu'er, why get so bent out of shape?
Shameless! You...
[Chu Liu'er, the eldest daughter
of the Chu family]
[Yun, a maid in the Chu Mansion]
Mr. Chu, you're finally back!
Liu'er, what's going on?
It's nothing.
Don't worry.
[Chu Qing, a disciple of the Chu family]
What brings you here, Mr. Chu Qing,
the talent of the Chu family?
You're just in time.
I'm going to marry your elder sister
as per the Grand Elder's order.
Marry?
You're reaching for the moon!
In your dreams!
Don't act rashly.
Chu Qing is the Grand Elder's godson.
A bright future awaits him.
Once they get married,
you become a family.
This way,
you can peacefully live out
the rest of your life.
You can't even cultivate.
How are you supposed
to protect your sister?
Getting her to marry Chu Qing
is the best bet.
Ms. Lin, you're super gifted.
I naturally can't compare
as an average person.
At least you have a hint
of self-awareness.
Our engagement is bound
to be called off sooner or later.
Without me having you under my wing,
you won't last a day in the Chu Mansion.
Under your wing?
Ms. Lin, you must be kidding.
Don't think
that I, Chu Kuangsheng,
care about our engagement.
That'd be the best.
Seems like you have a good sense of tact.
Any gripes
about me marrying your sister...
then?
Stop it! I'm down with your...
Liu'er,
we can't!
[Challenge letter]
This is my challenge letter to you,
the top talent of the Chu family.
Are you challenging me to a duel?
Three months down the line,
you and I will have a duel.
If I go down,
you can do whatever you want with me.
But if you bite the dust,
the engagement between you
and my sister is off.
And you never set foot in this mansion!
You're on!
Once your sister gets married,
I will arrange a shop for you
so that you can peacefully spend
the rest of your life.
Well, then... Ms. Lin, thanks a bunch.
It's no big deal to me.
You shouldn't have challenged
Chu Qing to a duel.
Liu'er, no worries.
In three months, I'll show them
that we siblings
are not ones to be messed with.
I believe in Mr. Chu!
(Something seems different
about Kuangsheng.)
Liu'er!
Ms. Chu!
Go get some medicine
to alleviate Liu'er's condition.
I'm going to gather herbs
in the mountains.
Where did Kuangsheng come
up with all this money?
There are many spiritual herbs growing
on this mountain,
but ordinary people can't recognize them.
Finally, got them all.
Pity that these herbs can only alleviate
Liu'er's pain temporarily.
They can't fix it for good.
Who's there? Show yourself!
Never thought a loser
like you'd have the guts
[Chu Yan, a disciple of the Chu family]
to challenge my brother.
(Chu Yan, that pig!)
(He harassed Ms. Qiu publicly a year ago,)
(nearly causing a disaster
for the Chu family.)
(If it weren't
for Chu Qing's intervention,)
(he'd have been expelled
from the Chu family long ago.)
You guys came here just to say this?
Give me those herbs,
or I won't pull any punches with you.
Then it's all yours.
There I was thinking this guy
had toughened up with time.
Turns out he's still a wimp.
Destined to be a loser.
You think you can just
walk away like that?
Three months later,
after he teaches that loser a lesson,
Senior Chu Qing can finally bring
the beauty home.
You bet. As for those girls
form the Ya Pavilion...
Our turf.
If you enjoy it, take your sweet time.
What's got you so happy?
Spill it. Let's all have
a good laugh together.
Who... Who are you? What do you want?
I've been feeling the urge lately.
Looking for someone to spar with.
- Fierce?
Fierce?
I don't buy
that he alone can make any waves.
Gang up on him!
How formidable!
Hand over everything
you've got.
Fierce, don't go too far.
What a load of rubbish.
Thank you for the gift,
then I'll gladly accept it.
Are you tailing me?
How can you call it tailing?
I just happened to pass by here.
I never thought that the renowned Fierce
would actually be the useless young master
of the Chu family.
You saw it all?
Would you believe me
if I say I didn't see anything?
Are you planning to kill me, Mr. Chu?
Can you really bring yourself to do it?
I'm not one of the righteous.
Don't try to seduce me.
Swallow this.
What's that?
Poison. Only I have the antidote.
What if I don't swallow it?
Just you wait, you scoundrel!
Sooner or later, you'll be sorry.
Oh no!
[Advertisement]